What are some things that you look for in
a company that you really want to invest in?
A group that we've created, a company
that has about $50 million to invest.
We're considered venture, so we do very early rounds.
We look for really interesting
ideas, really thoughtful management teams,
and we look for large kind of target markets.
So most of the investments we make
are somewhere between a half a million dollars
and maybe two or three million dollars.
There are companies that are generating
probably less than $2 million in revenue.
And then we focus those, get them
organized, help them hire really good talent,
and make sure they stay focused on the things.
As a young entrepreneur, as a CEO, sometimes
there's so many things coming at you at once,
and you have so few people to deal
with that you really don't know what matters.